(Silence; Operating Room Area)
=Stand Up for Love=
=Episode 24=
What are you trying to do?
(For Rent)
When we were together,
didn't you say you wanted
to see my home?
This is my home.
Let me make your wish come true.
Didn't you say
you'd only love me after you died?
Stop, Zhang Haotian!
Money couldn't buy Jiang Lai's kidney.
So you manipulated her with love.
Back then, you made me believe
Zhao Ke was seducing you.
You wanted me to get rid of her for you.
Because you were afraid she
was Jiang Lai.
You were afraid your scheme
would be exposed!
Are you done?
No!
You used to be by my side every day,
but suddenly, you started traveling
to North America all the time.
I looked into it.
You have no work records
in North America.
Zhang Haotian,
I truly loved you.
I really didn't want to believe
that you've been lying to me all along.
But
I can't keep fooling myself anymore.
So,
I let you see
the trust fund my mother left me.
Zhang Haotian, who desperately
wanted a divorce,
changed completely after seeing
the trust fund.
You started loving me again.
You shattered my last hope in you.
Zhang Haotian, from beginning to end,
the only thing you loved
was my money!
Get out!
Haotian.
Stop this.
Don't come closer!
Run. He's lost his mind.
Run!
Haotian.
No.
Run.
Zhang Haotian.
I just wanted to live a normal life.
To have enough food and warm clothes.
Was I wrong?
What did I do wrong?
Tell me!
Say it!
Didn't you say
you'd only love me if you died?
I don't mind.
I can make it happen for you.
Then we'll get married
and have our wedding.
Just you and me.
I can accept that.
Ke.
This time,
you finally love me.
I can finally have you.
You finally love me.
(Police)
Move! Hurry!
Zhang Haotian!
Let Jiang Lai go!
Who is Jiang Lai?
You have the wrong person.
She's my wife.
Her name is Zhao Ke.
She's Jiang Lai.
You and Chen Ping tricked Jiang Lai
into giving up her kidney.
And you committed financial fraud.
I've already handed the evidence
over to the police.
You...
Stop this now!
Don't hurt anyone else!
Zhang Haotian.
Your accomplice Chen Ping has already
been arrested at the airport.
(For Rent)
There's no point resisting anymore.
Let her go!
I wanted you to love me.
I wanted you dead.
So I have to do it myself.
Whether you do it or not,
it's already over.
Don't you understand?
Don't you all know?
That scumbag Wang treated me like a dog!
I've been bullied my whole life.
I've been humiliated again and again.
But even if I die,
I'll die with dignity.
Ke.
I can decide my own fate.
And I can still...
And I can still make sure...
you remember me forever.
Haotian! Haotian!
Jiang Lai, are you okay?
Haotian, wake up!
Haotian! Haotian!
No! Haotian!
Haotian!
Haotian! Haotian!
(A lost path leads to ruin.
A path of light leads afar.)
(Defendants Zhang Haotian
and Chen Ping,)
(after a public trial,
the court has found that)
(you exploited people's kindness
and trust)
(to carry out a series
of serious fraud schemes.)
(You have severely violated citizens'
personal and property rights,)
(and undermined public order, morality,
and the foundation of trust.)
(The overwhelming evidence leaves
your crimes undeniable.)
(The law,)
(as the final safeguard of fairness
and justice,)
(will not allow anyone
to trample upon it.)
(Defendant Chen Ping)
(is convicted of illegal organ
trafficking and intentional homicide.)
(You are sentenced
to twenty years in prison.)
(Jiang Lai)
(I believe the championship
will definitely be yours.)
(The End)
(Thank you for staying with us
on this journey.)
(May every viewer find)
(the love and care they deserve
in life,)
(and be surrounded by warmth
and kindness.)
♪Listen, the wind chimes softly whisper♪
♪I should forget you♪
♪But I have the will,
yet not the strength♪
♪To carry on♪
♪The scenery you once longed to see♪
♪You no longer have the strength♪
♪You want me to go there for you♪
♪I look up and see a hollow sky♪
♪Your freedom♪
♪Has become my cage♪
♪My hand brushes over your smile
in the photograph♪
♪This glass of wine is filled
with sorrow♪
♪I look up at the beautiful night sky♪
♪You told me♪
♪I would shine like a star♪
♪But you forgot to teach me♪
♪How to live without you♪
♪I look up at the starry sky♪
♪So hazy and blurred♪